Guide to the Dale R. Corson papers, 1963-1977
Corson, Dale R. papers, 1963-1977
- Series I. Administrative Papers
  - 1972-1973
    - Cornell University Medical College -Joint Administrative Board., 1973 (Box 69, Folder 37-41)
    - Cornell University Medical College -Joint Administrative Board., 1973-74 (Box 69, Folder 42)
    - New York Hospital - Cornell Medical Center School of Nursing., 1972 (Box 70, Folder 1)
      Abdellah, Faye G.
    - New York Hospital - Cornell Medical Center School of Nursing., 1972 (Box 70, Folder 2)
    - New York Hospital - Cornell Medical Center School of Nursing., 1972 (Box 70, Folder 3)
    - New York Hospital - Cornell Medical Center School of Nursing., 1972-73 (Box 70, Folder 4)
      Lambertsen, Eleanor C. National League for Nursing.
    - New York Hospital - Cornell Medical Center School of Nursing - Self Evaluation Report., 1972 (Box 70, Folder 5-6)
    - Sloan Kettering Cancer Center., 1972-73 (Box 70, Folder 7-10)
    - Collaborations in Art, Science and Technology (CAST)., 1971-72 (Box 70, Folder 11)
      Scala, Joseph.
    - CNYPIRG., 1972-73 (Box 70, Folder 12)
    - Commencement. Mizener, Arthur M., 1972-73 (Box 70, Folder 13)
    - Commencement., 1972-73 (Box 70, Folder 14)
      McManus, John F. Committee on Commencement Arrangements.
    - Commencement., 1972-73 (Box 70, Folder 15)
      Hall, Jackson O.; Ginsburg, Ralph. Student Finance Commission.
    - Commencement., 1972-73 (Box 70, Folder 16)
    - Narcotics., 1971-72 (Box 70, Folder 17)
      McLellan, Elizabeth S.; Gurowitz, William D. Safety Division; Hamilton College.
    - Narcotics., 1972 (Box 70, Folder 18)
      COSEP; Policy Notebook for Students.
    - Narcotics., 1972 (Box 70, Folder 19)
      George, Lowell T. Drug Education Committee; Safety Division.
    - Narcotics., 1972-73 (Box 70, Folder 20)
      Sullivan, William P.; Jones, William D. Safety Division.
    - Glee Club. Kaplan, Jonathan M., 1973 (Box 70, Folder 21)
    - Higher Education - Bundy Money., 1971 (Box 70, Folder 22)
      New York State Bundy Program; New York State Education Department
    - Higher Education - Bundy Money. Mercer, Norman A. New York State Education Department, 1971-72 (Box 70, Folder 23)
    - Higher Education - Bundy Money., 1973 (Box 70, Folder 24)
    - Higher Education - Keppel Commission. Lauber, John G.; Keppel, Francis; Phillips, Ellis L., 1973 (Box 70, Folder 25)
    - Higher Education - Keppel Commission., 1972-73 (Box 70, Folder 26)
    - Higher Education - Keppel Commission., 1972 (Box 70, Folder 27)
      Kirkpatrick, John I.; Nyquist, Ewald B.; Wilson, John D.
    - Higher Education - Keppel Commission. DRC Statement before Keppel Commission., 1972 (Box 70, Folder 28)
    - Higher Education - Keppel Commission. Beebee, Alexander M.; Hollander, T. Edward., 1973 (Box 70, Folder 29)
    - Higher Education - Miscellaneous., 1971-72 (Box 70, Folder 30)
      Chandler, John W.; Barlow, J. Robert; Eggers, Melvin A.
    - Higher Education - Miscellaneous. McGill, William J. Task Force on the Financing of Higher Education in New York State (Hurd Committee)., 1972 (Box 70, Folder 31)
    - Higher Education - Miscellaneous. Barlow, J. Robert., 1972 (Box 70, Folder 32)
    - Higher Education - Miscellaneous., 1972 (Box 70, Folder 33)
      Hurd, T. Norman. State aid to private institutions of higher education.
    - Higher Education - Miscellaneous., 1972 (Box 70, Folder 34)
      Hollander, T. Edward.
    - Higher Education - Miscellaneous., 1972 (Box 70, Folder 35)
      Boyer, Ernest L. DRC notes.
    - Higher Education - Miscellaneous., 1972 (Box 70, Folder 36)
      Rockefeller, Nelson A.; Anderson, Warren M.; Lindsay, John V. National Academy of Education.
    - Higher Education - Miscellaneous., 1972-73 (Box 70, Folder 37)
      Phillips, John D.; Kibbee, Robert J.
    - Higher Education - Miscellaneous. Cook, Constance E., 1973 (Box 70, Folder 38)
    - Higher Education - Miscellaneous., 1973 (Box 70, Folder 39)
      Heyns, Roger W.; Kidd, Charles V. New York State Education Department
    - Higher Education - Miscellaneous., 1973 (Box 70, Folder 40)
      Linowitz, Sol M.; Peterson, Martha; Muller, Steven.
    - Higher Education - Miscellaneous. Henle, Robert J., 1973 (Box 70, Folder 41)
    - Higher Education - Miscellaneous., 1973 (Box 70, Folder 42)
    - Higher Education - Henderson Committee. Henderson, Charles D. New York State Commission to Study the Causes of Campus Unrest., 1973 (Box 71, Folder 1)
    - Higher Education - Miscellaneous Bills. Wilkins, Roy., 1972 (Box 71, Folder 2)
    - Higher Education - Plan of Action. Muller, Steven; Hester, James M., 1972-73 (Box 71, Folder 3)
    - Higher Education - Nyquist's Advisory Council., 1973 (Box 71, Folder 4)
      New York State Regents Commission on Doctoral Education.
    - Higher Education - Nyquist's Advisory Council., 1971-73 (Box 71, Folder 5)
      Nyquist, Ewald B. New York State Regents Commission on Doctoral Education; DRC notes
    - Higher Education - Nyquist's Advisory Council., 1972 (Box 71, Folder 6)
      Nyquist, Ewald B.; Hollander, T. Edward. New York State Regents Commission on Doctoral Education.
    - Higher Education - Nyquist's Advisory Council., 1973 (Box 71, Folder 7)
      Piskor, Frank P.; Nyquist, Ewald B.
    - New York State Education Department, 1972 (Box 71, Folder 8)
      McGovern, Joseph W.; Wilson, John D.
    - New York State Education Department, 1973 (Box 71, Folder 9)
    - New York State Education Department, 1973 (Box 71, Folder 10)
    - David R. Korn Incident., 1972 (Box 71, Folder 11)
    - Miscellaneous News Articles., 1971-72 (Box 71, Folder 12)
    - Miscellaneous News Articles., 1972-73 (Box 71, Folder 13)
    - Social Events., 1972 (Box 71, Folder 14)
    - Social Events., 1972-73 (Box 71, Folder 15)
    - Student Employment., 1965 (Box 71, Folder 16)
      Committee on Student Employment Policy; Minimum wage.
    - Student Employment., 1967-72 (Box 71, Folder 17)
      Lee, Gary A.; Gurowitz, William D. Committee on Student Employment Policy.
    - Student Housing - Cooperatives., 1970-72 (Box 71, Folder 18)
      Darling, Ruth W.; Gurowitz, William D. Ujamaa Residential College; Telluride Association.
    - Student Housing - Fraternities., 1971-72 (Box 71, Folder 19)
      Psi Upsilon.
    - Student Housing - Miscellaneous., 1972 (Box 71, Folder 20)
      Henderson, David B. Group Housing Plan; Balch Hall.
    - Student Housing - Miscellaneous., 1972-73 (Box 71, Folder 21)
      Housing shortage; Cornell University Apartment Housing.
    - Interfraternity Council., 1969-7Q (Box 71, Folder 22)
    - Interfraternity Council., 1970-72 (Box 71, Folder 23)
    - Student Housing - Residence Plan., 1970-72 (Box 71, Folder 24)
      Gurowitz, William D. Kappa Delta; Chi Phi.
    - Students Miscellaneous., 1970-72 (Box 71, Folder 25)
      Tarassov, Nikolai K. Youth Against McGovern; Political activity; International Affairs Association; Operation Bridgehead.
    - Student Records Policies., 1968 (Box 71, Folder 26)
      Selective Service.
    - Student Records Policies., 1968 (Box 71, Folder 27)
    - Student Records Policies., 1968-69 (Box 71, Folder 28)
      Brock, Stephen C.; Mackesey, Thomas W. Selective Service.
    - Student Records Policies., 1969-72 (Box 71, Folder 29)
      Vaughan, Henry G. Stanford University.
    - SUNY-Cornell Task Force., 1969-73 (Box 71, Folder 30)
      Adams, Morton; Boyer, Ernest L. State Relationships Committee.
    - SUNY., 1970-72 (Box 71, Folder 31)
      Barton, Donald W. Two year colleges.
    - SUNY., 1971-72 (Box 71, Folder 32)
      Committee on Master Planning for Higher Education.
    - SUNY., 1971-73 (Box 71, Folder 33)
      Hollander, T. Edward. New York State Education Department
    - Teaching Assistants., 1968-70 (Box 71, Folder 34)
      Cooke, W. Donald; Howland, Bradford. Commission on Teaching Assistants.
    - Tuition., 1971-73 (Box 71, Folder 35)
      Jackson, R. Peter.
    - Universities Miscellaneous., 1971-72 (Box 71, Folder 36)
      University of Heidelberg.
    - University Senate Minutes., 1972 (Box 71, Folder 37)
    - University Senate Minutes., 1972-73 (Box 71, Folder 38)
    - University Senate Minutes., 1973 (Box 71, Folder 39-40)
    - University Senate - Correspondence., 1972 (Box 71, Folder 41)
      Purcell, Robert W.; Gurowitz, William D.; Norton, Mary Beth. Student trustees; Lettuce boycott.
    - University Senate - Correspondence., 1972-73 (Box 71, Folder 42)
      Gurowitz, William D.; Whitlock, John H. Faculty Council of Representatives; Dogs on campus.
    - University Senate - Correspondence., 1973 (Box 71, Folder 43)
      Minella, Raymond J.; Steele, Finley M.
    - University Senate - Letters of Transmittal., 1972 (Box 72, Folder 1)
      Levy, Harold O.; Gardner, Robert E.
    - University Senate - Letters of Transmittal., 1972-73 (Box 72, Folder 2)
      Norton, Mary Beth.
    - University Senate - Letters of Transmittal., 1972-73 (Box 72, Folder 3)
    - University Senate - Letters of Transmittal., 1973 (Box 72, Folder 4)
      Minella, Raymond J.
    - University Senate - Trustees. Danowitz, Jane P.; Gibbs, James L.; Parker, Gail Thain., 1971-73 (Box 72, Folder 5)
    - University Senate - Roster., 1972-73 (Box 72, Folder 6)
    - Admissions Criteria., 1973 (Box 72, Folder 7)
    - Calendar Committee., 1972-73 (Box 72, Folder 8)
    - Committee on Campus Life., 1972-73 (Box 72, Folder 9)
    - Committee on Campus Life., 1973 (Box 72, Folder 10)
      Berkey, Arthur L.
    - Committee on Campus Life Budget., 1973 (Box 72, Folder 11)
    - Committee on Codes., 1972-73 (Box 72, Folder 12)
    - Committee on Committees., 1972-73 (Box 72, Folder 13)
      Chamberlain, Robert L.
    - Committee on Committees., 1973 (Box 72, Folder 14)
    - Committee on Educational Innovation., 1972-73 (Box 72, Folder 15)
      Everett, Chestyn. Agency for Educational Innovation.
    - University Senate Executive Committee., 1972-73 (Box 72, Folder 16)
    - Judiciary Committee., 1972-73 (Box 72, Folder 17)
      Tannen, Louis N.
    - Judiciary Committee., 1972 (Box 72, Folder 18-20)
    - Committee on Military Training., 1972 (Box 72, Folder 21)
    - University Senate Resolution on Sex Discrimination., 1971-72 (Box 72, Folder 22)
    - Cohn Farm., 1968-71 (Box 72, Folder 23)
      Baskervllle, Alton; Sheinkman, Jacob; Friedland, William H. University Senate; New York State AFL-CIO; Migrant labor.
    - Cohn Farm., 1971 (Box 72, Folder 24)
      Palm, Charles E.; Boiler, Arthur C.; Greenwald, Eliot J. Committee on Minority and Disadvantaged Interests.
    - Cohn Farm., 1971 (Box 72, Folder 25)
      Kahn, Alfred E.; Catherwood, Martin P.; Hertzel, Catherine Cohn; Palm, Charles E. Cohn Foundation.
    - Planning Review Committee., 1972-73 (Box 72, Folder 26)
      Solomon, Harry.
    - Associations Miscellaneous., 1971 (Box 72, Folder 27)
      National Endowment for the Humanities; International Research and Exchanges Board; Universities Research Association, Inc.
    - Associations Miscellaneous., 1971-72 (Box 72, Folder 28)
      United States Office of Education; Associated Universities, Inc.; Brookhaven National Laboratory.
    - Associations Miscellaneous., 1972-73 (Box 72, Folder 29)
      Universities Research Association, Inc.
    - Associations Miscellaneous., 1973 (Box 72, Folder 30)
      National Commission on Accrediting.
    - Association of American Universities., 1972 (Box 72, Folder 31)
    - Association of American Universities., 1972-73 (Box 72, Folder 32-34)
    - Association of American Universities., 1973 (Box 72, Folder 35)
    - Association of American Universities., 1973 (Box 72, Folder 36)
      DRC notes.
    - American Council on Education., 1972 (Box 72, Folder 37)
    - American Council on Education., 1972 (Box 72, Folder 38)
      Heyns, Roger W.; Honey, John C.
    - American Council on Education., 1972-73 (Box 72, Folder 39)
      Office of Urban Affairs.
    - American Council on Education., 1972-73 (Box 72, Folder 40)
      Heyns, Roger W.
    - American Council on Education., 1973 (Box 72, Folder 41-42)
    - Association of Colleges and Univs. of the State of New York., 1972 (Box 72, Folder 43)
      Ingalls, Lester W.; Chandler, John W. DRC notes.
    - Commission on Independent Colls. and Univs., State of New York., 1971 (Box 72, Folder 44)
      Chandler, John W.; Mortola, Edward J.
    - Commission on Independent Colls. and Univs., State of New York., 1971-72 (Box 72, Folder 45)
      Kirkpatrick, John I.; Chandler, John W.
    - Commission on Independent Colls. and Univs., State of New York., 1972 (Box 72, Folder 46-47)
    - Commission on Independent Colls. and Univs., State of New York., 1972 (Box 73, Folder 1)
      Kirkpatrick, John I.; Bartlett, Kenneth. DRC notes.
    - Commission on Independent Colls. and Univs., State of New York., 1972-73 (Box 73, Folder 2)
      Kirkpatrick, John I.; Duryea, Perry.
    - Commission on Independent Colls. and Univs., State of New York., 1973 (Box 73, Folder 3)
      Kirkpatrick, John I.; Wilson, John D.
    - Commission on Independent Colls. and Univs., State of New York., 1973 (Box 73, Folder 4)
      Kirkpatrick, John I.
    - Five Associated University Libraries., 1972 (Box 73, Folder 5)
      Kaser, David.
    - Ivy Group Policy Committee., 1972 (Box 73, Folder 6)
      Sanford, Terry.
    - Ivy Group Policy Committee., 1972 (Box 73, Folder 7)
    - Ivy Group Policy Committee., 1972-73 (Box 73, Folder 8)
      Financial Aid Policy.
    - Ivy Group Policy Committee., 1973 (Box 73, Folder 9-11)
    - National Aeronautics and Space Administration. Low, George M., 1971 (Box 73, Folder 12)
    - National Association of State Univs. and Land-Grant Colleges., 1972 (Box 73, Folder 13)
      Varner, D. B.
    - National Association of State Univs. and Land-Grant Colleges., 1972 (Box 73, Folder 14)
      Huitt, Ralph K.
    - National Association of State Univs. and Land-Grant Colleges., 1972 (Box 73, Folder 15)
      Arnold, Christian K.
    - National Association of State Univs. and Land-Grant Colleges., 1972 (Box 73, Folder 16-17)
    - National Association of State Univs. and Land-Grant Colleges., 1973 (Box 73, Folder 18)
    - National Association of State Univs. and Land-Grant Colleges., 1973 (Box 73, Folder 19)
      Bankhead-Jones Funds.
    - Six Universities Group., 1972 (Box 73, Folder 20)
      Hester, James M.
    - Six Universities Group., 1972 (Box 73, Folder 21)
      Wilson, John D.; Finlay, James C.; Eggers, Melvin A.
    - Six Universities Group., 1972-73 (Box 73, Folder 22)
      Wilson, John D.
    - Foundations Miscellaneous., 1972-73 (Box 73, Folder 23)
      John Simon Guggenheim Memorial Foundation; Esso (Exxon) Education Foundation; Lasdon Foundation.
    - Department of Health, Education, and Welfare. Office for Civil Rights., 1972 (Box 73, Folder 24)
    - Department of Health, Education, and Welfare. Valentine, William R. Office for Civil Rights; Association of American Medical Colleges., 1972-73 (Box 73, Folder 25)
    - Department of Health, Education, and Welfare. Valentine, William R.; Weinberger, Caspar. Office for Civil Rights., 1972-73 (Box 73, Folder 26)
    - Carnegie Corporation., 1971-72 (Box 73, Folder 27)
      Scott, Robert A.; Robinson, David. Carnegie Commission.
    - Ford Foundation., 1971-72 (Box 73, Folder 28)
      Sviridoff, Mitchell; Carmichael, William D. Safety Division.
    - Ford Foundation., 1972-73 (Box 73, Folder 29)
      Bundy, McGeorge; Jones, Barclay G. New York State Urban Development Corporation.
    - Executive Staff Meeting Minutes., 1966-70 (Box 73, Folder 30-41)
    - Executive Staff Retreat., 1967 (Box 74, Folder 1)
    - Executive Staff Retreat., 1968-69 (Box 74, Folder 2-3)
      MOVE; Student housing.
    - Executive Staff Retreat., 1969 (Box 74, Folder 4-5)
    - Board of Trustees Appointments., 1970-71 (Box 74, Folder 6)
      Alumni Association.
    - Board of Trustees Appointments., 1971-73 (Box 74, Folder 7)
      Weiss, Stephen H.
    - Board of Trustees - General., 1972 (Box 74, Folder 8-10)
    - Board of Trustees - General., 1973 (Box 74, Folder 11)
    - Board of Trustees Committees -Miscellaneous., 1972-73 (Box 74, Folder 12)
    - Board of Trustees Committees -Miscellaneous., 1973 (Box 74, Folder 13)
    - Board of Trustees - Buildings and Properties Committee., 1972-73 (Box 74, Folder 14-16)
    - Board of Trustees - Committee on Communications., 1972 (Box 74, Folder 17-18)
    - Board of Trustees - Investment Committee., 1971-72 (Box 74, Folder 19-22)
    - Board of Trustees - Investment Advisory Committee., 1972-73 (Box 74, Folder 23-25)
    - Board of Trustees - Committee on Investment Policy and Social Action., 1971 (Box 74, Folder 26)
    - Board of Trustees Agenda, 12 July., 1972 (Box 74, Folder 27-28)
    - Board of Trustees Executive Committee Agenda, 20 Sept., 1972 (Box 74, Folder 29)
    - Board of Trustees Agenda, 13-14 Oct., 1972 (Box 74, Folder 30-31)
    - Board of Trustees Executive Committee Agenda, Oct. - Dec., 1972 (Box 74, Folder 32)
    - Board of Trustees Executive Committee Agenda, Jan., 1973 (Box 74, Folder 33)
    - Board of Trustees Agenda, 26-27 Jan., 1973 (Box 74, Folder 34)
    - Board of Trustees Executive Committee, 21 Feb., 15 Jan., 1973 (Box 74, Folder 35)
    - Board of Trustees Executive Committee, 15 Mar., 1973 (Box 74, Folder 36)
    - Board of Trustees Agenda, 16-17 Mar., 1973 (Box 74, Folder 37)
    - Board of Trustees Executive Committee, 18 Apr., 1973 (Box 74, Folder 38)
    - Board of Trustees Executive Committee, 23 May., 1973 (Box 74, Folder 39)
    - Board of Trustees Agenda, 24 May., 1973 (Box 75, Folder 1)
    - Budget 1973-74, Endowed Units., 1973 (Box 75, Folder 2)
    - Cornell University Libraries - Director Search Committee., 1973 (Box 75, Folder 3)
    - Cornell University Libraries - Director Search Committee., 1973-74 (Box 75, Folder 4)
    - Cornell University Libraries - Director Search - Nominations., 1973 (Box 75, Folder 5)
    - Cornell University Libraries - Director Search - Affirmative Action., 1973 (Box 75, Folder 6)
      Edelman, Hendrik. Black and women candidates.
    - Cornell University Libraries - Director Search - Affirmative Action., 1973 (Box 75, Folder 7)
      Rivera, Ramon E. Black and women candidates.
    - Cornell University Libraries - Director Search., 1973 (Box 75, Folder 8-27)
      Files on candidates, including biographical material, recommendations, and disposition.
    - Cornell University Libraries - Director Search - Follow-up., 1973-74 (Box 75, Folder 28)
      Miller, J. Gormly.
    - New York State College of Human Ecology Dean Search Committee., 1974 (Box 75, Folder 29)
      Knapp, David C.; Barlow, Mark.
    - New York State College of Human Ecology Dean Search Committee., 1974 (Box 75, Folder 30)
      "Affirmative Action Review of the Activities of the Search Committee Seeking a Dean for the New York State College of Human Ecology. "
    - New York State College of Human Ecology Dean Search - strong Candidates., 1974 (Box 75, Folder 31-32)
    - New York State College of Human Ecology Dean search - Candidates from College., 1974 (Box 75, Folder 33)
      Failing, Jean.
    - New York State College of Human Ecology Dean Search - "B" Candidates., 1974 (Box 75, Folder 34)
    - New York State college of Human Ecology Dean Search - "C" Candidates., 1974 (Box 75, Folder 35-40)
    - New York State College of Human Ecology Dean Search - Need More Information., 1974 (Box 75, Folder 41-42)
    - New York State College of Human Ecology Dean Search - Miscellaneous., 1974 (Box 76, Folder 1-3)
    - New York State Veterinary College Dean Search committee., 1974 (Box 76, Folder 4-5)
    - New York State Veterinary College Dean Search - Qualifications., 1974 (Box 76, Folder 6)
    - New York State Veterinary College Dean Search - Requests for Nominations., 1974 (Box 76, Folder 7)
    - New York State Veterinary College Dean Search - Nominations., 1974 (Box 76, Folder 8-12)
    - New York state veterinary College Dean Search - Candidates., 1974 (Box 76, Folder 13-20)
    - Africana studies and Research Center -Permanent File., 1973 (Box 76, Folder 21)
      Undergraduate major.
    - Africana Studies and Research Center -Budget., 1972 (Box 76, Folder 22)
      Turner, James E.; Carter, Lisle C.
    - Africana studies and Research Center -Budget., 1972 (Box 76, Folder 23)
      Turner, James E.; Carter, Lisle C.; Mbata, J. Congress; Farley, Jennie T. T. Master of Professional Studies.
    - Africana Studies and Research Center -Budget., 1972 (Box 76, Folder 24)
    - Africana Studies and Research Center -Accounts., 1971-72 (Box 76, Folder 25)
    - Africana Studies and Research Center., 1970-71 (Box 76, Folder 26)
      Urban Component; Ford Foundation.
    - Africana Studies and Research Center., 1969-70 (Box 76, Folder 27)
      Carter, Lisle C. "Report on a Visit to Africa"; Southside Summer Pre-School Program; Afro-American Society.
    - Africana Studies and Research Center., 1969-70 (Box 76, Folder 28-29)
    - Africana Studies and Research Center., 1969-72 (Box 76, Folder 30)
    - Africana Studies and Research Center -Meeting Minutes., 1972 (Box 76, Folder 31)
      Turner, James E.; Carter, Lisle C.; Billingsley, Andrew.
    - Africana Studies and Research Center -Meeting Minutes., 1972 (Box 76, Folder 32)
      Berry, Mary Francis. Africana Review Committee.
    - Africana Studies and Research Center -Press Coverage., 1971-72 (Box 76, Folder 33)
      Carter, Lisle C.
    - Africana Studies and Research center -Outgoing Correspondence., 1972 (Box 76, Folder 34)
      Berry, Mary Francis; Elias, Robert H.
    - Africana Studies and Research Center -Outgoing Correspondence., 1972 (Box 76, Folder 35)
      Berry, Mary Francis; Carter, Lisle C.; Brooks, Gwendolyn; Billingsley, Andrew; Kahn, Alfred E.; Turner, James E.; Kennedy, W. Keith. Kahn's summary of COSEP Africana questionnaires.
    - Africana studies and Research Center -Xeroxed Material., 1972 (Box 76, Folder 36)
    - Africana Review Committee., 1972-73 (Box 76, Folder 37)
      Carter, Lisle C.; Turner, James E.
    - Africana Review Committee - Student Subcommittee., 1972-73 (Box 76, Folder 38)
      Cooke, W. Donald; Turner, James E.; Mbata, J. Congress.
    - Africana Report Material., 1972 (Box 76, Folder 39)
    - Africana Report Drafts., 1973 (Box 76, Folder 40-43)
    - COSEP Home Addresses., 1971-72 (Box 76, Folder 44-45)
    - COSEP Africana Student Questionnaire., 1973 (Box 76, Folder 46-47)
    - COSEP Africana Student Questionnaire., 1973 (Box 77, Folder 1-3)
    - Lisle C. Carter., 1973 (Box 77, Folder 4)
      Kahn, Alfred E.; Penney, Norman.
    - Center for International Studies. Ford Foundation., 1963-65 (Box 77, Folder 5)
    - Center for International Studies., 1965 (Box 77, Folder 6)
    - Center for International Studies., 1966 (Box 77, Folder 7)
      Mackesey, Thomas W.; Muller, Steven; Sharp, Lauriston. Committee on Soviet Studies.
    - Center for International Studies., 1966-67 (Box 77, Folder 8)
      Einaudi, Mario. Ford Foundation.
    - Center for International Studies., 1967-68 (Box 77, Folder 9)
      Einaudi, Mario.
    - Center for International Studies -Minutes., 1964-67 (Box 77, Folder 10)
    - Cornell Centers., 1962-65 (Box 77, Folder 11)
    - Certificates., 1964 (Box 77, Folder 12)
    - Chemistry., 1967 (Box 77, Folder 13)
    - College and School Councils., 1964-65 (Box 77, Folder 14)
    - Committee on Human Rights., 1964 (Box 77, Folder 15)
    - Policy on Inter-college Compensation., 1965 (Box 77, Folder 16)
    - Summer Compensation., 1966 (Box 77, Folder 17)
    - Statutory Colleges Academic Flans., 1965-66 (Box 77, Folder 18)
    - Committee on Student Evaluation of Teaching and Courses., E. d. (Box 77, Folder 19)